Baole, you want to destroy the dam! In the past, everyone listened to the phrase "the crisis of No. 0 Dam" as entertainment.
At the beginning of Baobao Fun, the No. 0 Dam was really in crisis. The dam originally has a lot of people,
There are more people now. Once you enter Dam Zero, you don't know whether you are playing Delta or Plants vs. Zombies.
On one side is the one holding a treasure image to poison the zombies, and on the other side is the King of Martial Arts zombie wearing five or six suits.
Once you get out, you can still use the Hidden Wind Formation technique, and then call out the two Xuanzhuang brothers.
In the past, No. 0 Dam was a gathering place for gods and men.
You never know who would sit in a dam car and order tons of games.
Now in the dam, you can really see the various expressions of all sentient beings, with five sets and six sets of full outfits, brother,
If you don't go to the administration building, go into the wild. There is also a small Bo Da who is very exciting and makes glass cannons.
There are also snipers on the top of the dam, ah, and some hiding treasure spots. You said that I squatted until the end as soon as I entered the game,
Why not just open a treasure chest? It's been the last ten minutes, and I haven't even gotten close to the treasure chest. The bullet came first. What happened?
Are you the Asara Protector and Tibetan Keeper? Of course, the most profound god has to be squatting at an ordinary evacuation point.
As soon as he entered the game, no matter which number one position he was given, he was too lazy to play, so he just ran to the extraction point.
When you reach the evacuation point, squat down there. Crouch down and start watching videos.
While listening to the footsteps, I got up as soon as there were footsteps.
Do you think any of the serious patrol teams on this map, Dad, are not the ones pulling the plug? You are the one who crouched down to uncover the treasure.
The treasure is only the size of two, and the safe can also fit in it. You tell your eldest father,
What exactly can you do while squatting in Big Dad’s car? Squat and squat,
In the end, I came across a bankrupt rat who wanted to be a girl even if he entered the big daddy. He said, "What are you trying to do?"